Guide to the Community, Food & Agriculture Program records, 1960-2000.
Community, Food & Agriculture Program records
- Cultivating Farm, Neighbor, and Community Relations (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Developing New Markets (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Developing New Markets 2 (Box 13, Folder 38)
- Directory of CCE Field Staff with Experience in Alternative Farm Enterprises (Box 13, Folder 39)
- Economic Impacts of Agriculture (Box 13, Folder 40)
- Educating The Public (Box 13, Folder 41)
- Educating The Pubic 2 (Box 13, Folder 42)
- Affective Farm Organizations: The Power of Cooperation (Box 13, Folder 43)
- Affective Farm Organizations (Box 13, Folder 44)
- FAP Brochures (Box 13, Folder 45)
- Engaging the Public (Box 14, Folder 1)
- FAP Publications (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Farmland Protection Planning (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Fostering Entrepreneurship Business Retention & Enhancement (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Horticulture Innovations Case Studies (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Horticulture Innovations Case Studies (Cont’d) (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Mobilizing The Community (Box 14, Folder 7)
- New Publications, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Urban Connections & Community Food Security (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Who Will Farm? (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Who Will Farm? 2 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Gil Gillespie, Jr. (Box 14, Folder 12)
- AG Enterprise Project (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Biodynamic Land Trust Project (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Enterprises, To Be Added To List (Box 14, Folder 15)
- ENT’s - Needing Addresses (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Ethics In Food System Dialogue Meeting (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Ethnic Markets & Sustainable Agriculture (Box 14, Folder 18)
- FADC Projects (Box 14, Folder 19)
- FADC Advisors (Box 14, Folder 20)
- FADC - Sources (Box 14, Folder 21)
- FADC - Stuff (Box 14, Folder 22)
- FAP Project Survey (Box 14, Folder 23)
- FAP Research Project (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Farmer Cooperation In Marketing Of Produce Project (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Farmers Market Project (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Finger Lakes Small Farm Marketing Project - Final Report (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Food Systems Project (Box 14, Folder 28)
- GreenStar (Box 14, Folder 29)
- GS Case Study (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Info Resources Project (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Info Revamp (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Kellogg Integrated Farming Systems project, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- KISS (Box 14, Folder 34)
- KIQ (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Spec. Vegetables (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Managing Change In AG: Educational (Box 14, Folder 37)
- FAP - Case Studies Back-Up Info (Box 14, Folder 38)
- Northeast Farmers’ Market As Incubators Project (Box 14, Folder 39)
- Onendaga County Farm-City Project (Box 14, Folder 40)
- The Potential (Box 14, Folder 41)
- The Role of Small Scale Fruit & Vegetable Grower Cooperatives in Sustaining Northeast Agriculture (Box 14, Folder 42)
- Shared Use Kitchens Project (Box 14, Folder 43)
- Sheep/Goat Marketing Project, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 44)
- Sustainable Food and Agriculture Systems (Box 15, Folder 1)
- SARE Report-Strategic Plan (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Tompkins County Ag and Food Project (Box 15, Folder 3)
- USDA Environmental Justice Strategy (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Who’s Looking Out for T. County Project (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Agricultural Entrepreneurship Project (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Alternative Agriculture Enterprise Database, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Community Agriculture Development Project Kellogg Proposal, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- FAC Proposal (Box 15, Folder 9)
- FADC Proposals (Box 15, Folder 10)
- FAP (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Funding Proposals (Box 15, Folder 12)
- Restructuring Proposal, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- SBIR Grant Proposal Commercial Scale Organic Herb Growing, Processing, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Small Scale Food Processing for Rural Development (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Ag and Markets, Contract Reports, Etc., 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Housing Cooperatives (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Merrimack Cooperative (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Natural Farmer’s Coop of St. Lawrence Valley (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Food and Justice Program (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Unidentified (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Alternative Food Production System- Chuck Mohler (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Menzies, Paul, NGFC (Box 15, Folder 23)
- NYWOF (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Public Forum, 12/4/1981 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- FM Focus Groups (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Unidentified (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Northeastern Farmers’ Markets Surveys #1, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Northeastern Farmers’ Markets Surveys #2-3, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Northeastern Farmers’ Markets Surveys #4-5, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Northeastern Farmers’ Markets Surveys #6-7, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Northeastern Farmers’ Markets Surveys #8-9, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Survey of USDA 1 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Survey of USDA 2 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Survey of USDA 3 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Farming Alternatives Project (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Farming Alternatives Project 2 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Phone Interview Summary (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Questionnaire 1993, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Survey-Master List (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Sustainable Dam, Farming - Phone Interviews (Box 16, Folder 9)
- AG Development (Box 16, Folder 10)
- AG Economic Development (Box 16, Folder 11)
- AG Industry News (Box 16, Folder 12)
- AG Industry News 2 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Agribusiness (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Agricultural Team Building (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Agriculture & Farming - NYS (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Agriculture & Farming - Tompkins County (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Agriculture Policy Studies (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Agriculture Productivity Act (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Agritourism (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Agroforestry (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Alternative AG., Institute For (Box 16, Folder 22)
- AG Statistics (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Alternative Enterprises (Box 16, Folder 24)
- American Agriculture - Gen. (Box 16, Folder 25)
- US Committee on Science and Technology (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Community AG Development (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Community Agriculture Development (Box 17, Folder 1)
- SARE Strat/Plan Project Inservice Implement, 1995-1996 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Community Planning (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Conflict Management (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Cooperative Banks (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Cooperatives (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Core Values (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Dairy (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Economic Development (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Farm Characteristics (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Farm Debt (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Farm Financial Situation (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Farmer’s Home Administration (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Farmland (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Farmland Protection (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Farmland Protection (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Farm Management (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Farm/Neighbor Conflict Resolution (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Farm Policy (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Farm Policy/ AG Policy (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Farmers Markets (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Farmworkers’ Struggles: The Campbell’s/Libby’s Boycott (Box 17, Folder 22)
- The Farmworker’s Stuggle: Financing (Box 17, Folder 23)
- The Farmworker’s Stuggle: General (Box 17, Folder 24)
- The Farmworker’s Stuggle (Box 17, Folder 25)
- The Farmworker’s Stuggle: Negro Workers (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Farmhands Inc (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Women & Development: Refining the Issues (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Festivals (Box 17, Folder 29)
- Food Banks (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Food Consumption: Supply and Demand (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Food Cooperatives Info (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Food and Nutrition (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Food & Agriculture Policy - General (Box 18, Folder 4)
- US Food & Agriculture Policy - 1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- US Food & Agriculture Policy - 1979 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- US Food & Agriculture Policy - 1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- US Food & Agriculture Policy - 1981 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- US Food & Agriculture Policy - 1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- US Food & Agriculture Policy - 1985 Farm Bill (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Farm Policy (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Food & Farm Policy 1973 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Food & Farm Policy 1979 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- NYS Food & Farm Policy 1980 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- New York State Food & Farm Policy 1981-1982 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- New York State Food & Farm Policy 1984 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- New York State Food & Farm Policy 1985 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- US Food & Farm Policy 1986 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Food & Energy Inputs (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Food Issues (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Hunger (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Food Miles (Box 18, Folder 22)
- Food Policy (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Food Production (Box 18, Folder 24)
- Food Systems (Box 18, Folder 25)
- Food Systems 2 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Food Systems 3 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Horticulture (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Labels (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Land Tax Assessment (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Land Use Regulations (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Local Food Systems (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Decrease In Farmland (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Rural Economics (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Entry Into Farming (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Resource Information (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Reference Articles (Box 19, Folder 12)
- News Clippings (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Patenting (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Crops (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Biol & Soc Seminars (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Farming Alternative Program Tours (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Cooperative Extension (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Agritourism RC & D (Utica) (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Blobaum’s Meeting/Talk, 10/9/1992 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Conference Documents (Box 19, Folder 21)
- Conference Thank You’s (Box 19, Folder 22)
- Conference Expo (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Farming For The Future (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Farming For The Future (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Farming For The Future, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Farming For The Future, 3/12-13/1997 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Hudson Valley Workshop (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Monroe County Talk, 10/6/1992 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- SSFP Talk (Box 20, Folder 7)
- New York State SSFP Color Transparency (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Statewide Farming Alternatives Conference, Mar-88 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Unique & Develop Conference (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Western New York Workshop (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Workshops, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Transitions (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Workshop Model Packets, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Regional Home-based Business Conference, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Illinois C-FAR, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Closing The Food Circle (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Closing The Food Circle 2 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Conferences, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Conference Seminar Notes (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Society For Nutrition Education (Box 21, Folder 2)
- USDA - ERS Small Farms Workshop, Jul-99 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Conference Planning (Box 21, Folder 4)
- FAP Student Guide (Box 21, Folder 5)
- FAP Display, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Tour Planning (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Future Of Farming In NYS, November 1994 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Future Of Farming In NYS Dialogue Meeting, April 1995 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Group/Planning Process (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Program Evaluation (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Duncan Hilchey (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Duncan 3 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Duncan 4 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Auburn University (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Gil Gillespie (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Judy Green (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Judy Green Employment (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Judy Green’s Presentation Notes (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Judy Green’s Presentation/Overheads (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Agricultural Economic Development (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Agritourism in NYS: Opportunities and Challenges (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Engaging the Public in Local Agricultural Issues (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Ithaca Farmers Market (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Horticulture Innovators MASTER (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Two Small Mills in NYS (Box 21, Folder 26)
- Who Will Farm? (Box 21, Folder 27)
- Staff Meetings: FAP Planning and Oversight (Box 22, Folder 1)
- CFAP Advisors (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Advisory Committee Notes (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Mission and Goals (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Enhanced Farmer-Non-Farmer Links (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Outreach (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Plan of Work (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Strategic Planning (Box 22, Folder 8)
- NYSDAM POW and budget, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- NYSDAM Contract, 1993-1994 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- FAP 4 Pager (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Contact Reports (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Reorganization Plan (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Staffing Plans (Box 22, Folder 14)
- CRIS Reports (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Faculty Fellows (Box 22, Folder 16)
- SSFP Study: Research Aide Position (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Workstudy (Box 22, Folder 18)
- LHB Institute (Box 22, Folder 19)
- USDA Props Review (Box 22, Folder 20)
- CFAP Financial/Travels (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Office Organizing (Box 22, Folder 22)
- CFAP Future (Box 22, Folder 23)
- CFAP Vision (Box 22, Folder 24)
- DH Impact (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Liberty Hyde Bailey (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Dream Project (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Hatch: Consumers (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Growing Home Endorsement (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Computer Stuff (Box 22, Folder 30)
- CFAP Staff Meetings (Box 22, Folder 31)
- GEN: Mann Library (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Small Scale Co-Op Project (Box 22, Folder 33)
- CARDI Innovator (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Value Added for Sust. (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Value Adding (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Unidentified (Box 22, Folder 37)
- SSFP (Box 22, Folder 38)
- SSFP: Trade Associations (Box 22, Folder 39)
- SSFP (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Value Added Guidebook (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Albany Small Farms Testimony (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Small Scale Farms (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Small Ruminants Project (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Meat Goat (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Meat Goats (Box 22, Folder 46)
- Small Ruminants Project (Box 22, Folder 47)
- Northeast Agricultural Development Symposium- part I (Box 22, Folder 48)
- Northeast Agricultural Development Symposium- part II (Box 22, Folder 49)
- FAP Info Packets (I) (Box 22, Folder 50)
- FAP Info Packets (II) (Box 22, Folder 51)
- Exploring the Opportunities for Agroforestry in Changing Rural Landscapes, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 52)
- An Analysis of the Economic Dimension of the New York State Greenhouse Industry, Sept. 1999 (Box 22, Folder 53)
- Toward 2005: Northeast Agriculture, Food and Forestry—Issues and Opportunities, 4/24/1987 (Box 22, Folder 54)
- Processed Apple Product Marketing Analysis: Apple Juice and Cider, Jan. 2001 (Box 22, Folder 55)
- Processed Apple Product Marketing Analysis: Hard Cider and Apple Wine, Jun-00 (Box 22, Folder 56)
- Thinking Afresh About Processing: An Exploration of New Market Opportunities for Apple Products, Jun-01 (Box 22, Folder 57)
- FAP Info Packets III (Box 23, Folder 1)
- FAP Info Packets IV (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Farming Alternatives Articles (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Farming Alternatives- Statements and Reports (Box 23, Folder 4)
- FAP- Reports, Presentations, Memos (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Deer Information (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Correspondence and FAP Publicity (Box 23, Folder 7)
- FAP Planning (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Tom Lyson (Box 23, Folder 9)
- CUSA/CU Sust. Ag. Adv. Com. (Box 23, Folder 10)
- CUSA First Meeting, Jun-94 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Judy Green: CU Working Group for Sustainable food and Ag Systems (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Working Group (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Examples of Proposals (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Proposal Writing Info (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Working Group Self-Assessment (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Proposal Participants (Task Force, Review Committee) (Box 23, Folder 17)
- SARE Vt. Meeting, Nov. 29-Dec.1 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- FAP Planning, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Old Plans (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Quarterly Reports (Box 23, Folder 21)
- JG Brouhaha, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- NY RDC Ag/NR Work Group (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Study Tours (Box 24, Folder 1)
- NGTSN Judy G. Part 1, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- NGTSN Judy G. Part 2, 1999 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Northeast Agricultural Development Symposium Pt. 1, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Northeast Agricultural Development Symposium Pt. 2, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Agriculture and Economic Development (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Urban Connections/ Who Will Farm (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Opportunities/Market/Conflict (Box 24, Folder 8)
- FAP Marketing and Outreach, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- NYS Budget Quest (Box 24, Folder 10)
- JG Plan/Portfolio/Report (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. I Overviews Pt. 1, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. I Overviews Pt. 2, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. II- Mgt. The Whole Farm Pt. 1, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. II- Mgt. The Whole Farm Pt. 2, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. II- Mgt. The Whole Farm Pt. 3, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. III- Mgt. Soils and Crops Pt. 1, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. III- Mgt. Soils and Crops Pt. 2, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. III- Mgt. Soils and Crops Pt. 3, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. III- Mgt. Soils and Crops Pt. 4, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. III- Mgt. Soils and Crops Pt. 5, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. IV- Livestock Mgt. Pt. 1, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. IV- Livestock Mgt. Pt. 3, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Sustainable Farming: Compendium Vol. IV- Livestock Mgt. Pt. 4, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Budget (Box 25, Folder 3)
- AFC Partnership (Box 25, Folder 4)
- LHBC (Box 25, Folder 5)
- CFAP Advisory (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Farm Tour Budget (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Budworth Farm (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Agritourism Case Studies (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Agritourism Conferences (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Agriculture and Tourism- General (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Agritourism General Tourism Pubs (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Listings (Agritourism) (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Marketing Items (Agritourism) (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Other Recreation/Services (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Ag-Tourism Presentation (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Unidentified (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Key FAP Documents (Box 26, Folder 6)
- FAP Reports- Part 1 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- FAP Reports- Part 2 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Food Processing Articles (Box 26, Folder 9)
- The Power of Food (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Various Papers (Box 26, Folder 11)
- FAP Bibliography (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Farming Alternatives (Box 26, Folder 13)
- New York Agriculture Part 1 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- New York Agriculture Part 2 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Unidentified (Box 26, Folder 16)
- FFF Conference, Feb-95 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- FAP Budget, Impacts, Planning, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Dialogue Series (Box 26, Folder 19)
- CU Update (Box 27, Folder 1)
- CUWG SFAS (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Big Apple and Orange Ag. Dev. Study Tour, 1998 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Northeast Hop Alliance (Box 27, Folder 4)
- NYS R&D Grant Program-general (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Farming for the Future- Part I (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Farming for the Future- Part II (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Farming for the Future- Part III (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Farming Alternatives- Staff Meetings, Memos, Others- Part I (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Farming Alternatives- Staff Meetings, Memos, Others- Part II (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Farming Alternatives- Staff Meetings, Memos, Others- Part III (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Farming Alternatives- Staff Meetings, Memos, Others- Part IV (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Unidentified (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Northeast Ag. Symposium Part I (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Northeast Ag. Symposium Part II (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Videos
  - Farming Alternatives, V-5488 (Box 27)
  - Transitions Conference: Copy 1, General Session, 1990; V-5494 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Master, Vegetables/Small Fruits II, 1990; V-5496 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Livestock, Forages and Field Crops. AM Session. Includes Keynote Tom Frantzen, 1993; V-5502 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Janas Dairy, Moravia; Crescent Farm Bakery, Genoa; Osterhoudt, 1993; V-5500 (Box 28)
  - Transition Conference Master General Session and Dairy 1, 1990; V-5495 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: New Paltz, AM Session, Vegetables, 1993; V-5498 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Apple Production, Elizabeth Ryan, B. Anderson, David Gill, 1994; V-5503 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Dairy/Field Crops Session, Tape 2, 1991; V-5497 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Vegetables, AM Session, V.30.1, 1993; V-5499 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Vegetables, AM Session, V.30.2, 1993; V-5501 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Livestock 1-Grazing, Cover Crops, 1993; V-5446 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Livestock 2-Cover Crops, Cultivation, 1993; V-5445 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: PM Session, Specialty Dairy, 1993; V-5447 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Welcome and Introduction, Tape 1, 1990; V-5448 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Apples: V.31.1, 1993; V-5449 (Box 28)
  - Buy Local Campaigns Workshop, 2002; V-5450 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Marketing, 1992; V-5451 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Apples: AM Session, Orchard Management, 1993; V-5452 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Livestock 3-Holistic Research Management, Looking at Agriculture in a Broader Sense, 1993; V-5453 (Box 28)
  - Farming Alternatives, V-5454 (Box 28)
  - Sustainable Agriculture:Bill Thompson, Mike Kane, 1993; V-5455 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Dairy, Field Crops II, Master, 1990; V-5456 (Box 28)
  - Farming Alternatives Program, 1995; V-5457 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Agriculture in the Community, PM Session, V.34.2, 1993; V-5458 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Apples, AM Session, V.31.2, 1993; V-5459 (Box 28)
  - F.A.P.: Composting, 1994; V-5460 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Agriculture and the Community, Challenges and Solutions, Master, 1993; V-5461 (Box 28)
  - Farm Tourism Forum V.05.2, V-5462 (Box 28)
  - F.A.P. Regional Workshop: Crispin, Green, Yacuk, Entrepreneur Panel, V-5463 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Finding New Markets, Master, 1993; V-5464 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Developing Specialty Dairy Products, V.33.2, 1993; V-5465 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Fessenden, Smith, Cooperative Extension, 1994; V-5466 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Dairy/Field Crops Session 4.1, 1990; V-5467 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Developing Specialty Products, V.33.1, 1993; V-5468 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: General Sessions, Tape 1, 1991; V-5469 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Dairy/Field Crops Session 1, 1991; V-5470 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: AM Sessions, 1992; V-5471 (Box 28)
  - Farming Alternative Program, V-5472 (Box 28)
  - F.A.P. Regional Workshop Tape 2, V-5473 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Keynote, Master, 1993; V-5474 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Finding New Markets, V.32.1, 1993; V-5475 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Livestock, Forages and Field Crops, V.29.2, 1993; V-5476 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Fruits Session 1, 1990; V-5477 (Box 28)
  - Farming for the Future: Opening Panel Discussion, 1995; V-5478 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Fruits Session 1 Master, 1990; V-5479 (Box 28)
  - C.S.A, 1990; V-5480 (Box 28)
  - Buy Local Campaigns Workshop, Tape 1, 2002; V-5481 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Apples, PM Session, 1993; V-5482 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Dairy/Field Crops 3, 1990; V-5483 (Box 28)
  - Farming Alternatives: Innovations on Northeast Farms, V.04.2, V-5484 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Agricultural Farmland Protection, 1994; V-5485 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Fruits 2, 1994; V-5486 (Box 28)
  - Extension's Role in Environmental Policy Conflict, 1993; V-5487 (Box 28)
  - Paul Curtis: Vertebrate Pest Management, 1991; V-5489 (Box 28)
  - F.A.P. Regional Workshop: Woodlot Management-Gary Goff, V-5490 (Box 28)
  - Maple Syrup Production, V.25.M, V-5491 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Dairy and Field Crops II, 1990; V-5492 (Box 28)
  - Transitions Conference: Vegetables/Small Fruits I, 1990; V-5493 (Box 28)